Hula, Erich; Papers ger044
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Pamphlets, 8; 378 file folders
  - Gross, Leo.Voting in the Security Council: Abstention in the Post-1965 Amendment Phase and its Impact on Article 25 of the Chapter, 1968 July (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 35)
  - Grünberg, Carl.Das Grundgesetz der russischen Sowjetrepublik, 1919 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 36)
  - Gulick, Edward Vose.The Balance of Power, 1943 March (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 37)
  - Hamilton, Thomas J. and Vera Micheles Dean.Report on the United Nations, 1949 May 20 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 38)
  - Hammarskjold, Dag."A Service ... Profoundly Meaningful". Remarks by Secretary-General D.H. to the United Nations General Assembly following his election to a second term, 1957 November (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 39)
  - Hammarskjold, Dag.The Development of a Constitutional Framework for International Cooperation, 1960 June (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 40)
  - Hammarskjold, Dag.The United Nations - An Appraisal. Text of an Address Given by Secretary-General D.H. Before the Indian Council of World Affairs in New Delhi, India, February 3, 1956, 1956 April (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 41)
  - Handlin, Oscar et al.Dissent, Democracy and Foreign Policy - a Symposium, 1968 August (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 42)
  - Hartmann, Paul.Die Überprüfung der Gesetze nach tschechoslowakischem Rechte. Eine dogmatische Untersuchung, 1928 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 43)
  - Hayden, Sherman S. and Benjamin Rivlin.Non-self-governing Territories. Status of Puerto Rico, 1954 September (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 44)
  - Henderson, William.Pacific Settlement of Disputes: The Indonesian Question 1946-1949, 1954 September (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 45)
  - Hermens, Ferdinand A.Der Ost-West Konflikt. Gründe und Scheingründe, 1961 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 46)
  - Herz, John H.Germany, 1974 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 47)
  - Higgins, Rosalyn.The Administration of United Kingdom Foreign Policy through the United Nations, 1966 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 48)
  - Hold-Ferneck, Alexander.Ein Kampf ums Recht. Entgegnung auf Kelsens Schrift "Der Staat als Übermensch", 1927 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 49)
  - Hold-Ferneck, Alexander.Der Staat als Übermensch. Zugleich eine Auseinandersetzung mit der Rechtslehre Kelsens, 1926 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 50)
  - Holman, Frank E.An Address at a Meeting of the District of Columbia Bar Association, Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C., February 8, 1949, Undated (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 51)
  - Hoover, Herbert Jr.The Tasks of the Eleventh General Assembly, 1956 November 16 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 52)
  - Humphreys, John H.What is Proportional Representation? A Broadcast Talk, 1936 April (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 53)
  - Hutchins, Robert M.The Atomic Bomb versus Civilization, 1945 December (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 54)
  - Infiesta, Ramón.Martí, the Statesman, 1953 April 17 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 55)
  - Interdepartmental Committee on Cooperation with the American Republics.Constitution of the United States of Brazil, 1939 January (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 56)
  - International Bureau of the Universal Postal Union.The Universal Postal Union. Its Foundation and Development, 1955 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 57)
  - The International Commission of Jurists.The Rule of Law in the Federal Republic of Germany, 1958 December (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 58)
  - International Labour Conference.Twenty-ninth Session, Montreal. Provisional Record, 1946 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 59)
  - International Political Science Association.General Information, Undated (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 60)
  - Isensee, Josef, Ernst Friesenhahn, Werner Marx.Reden zum 50. Doktorjubiläum von Werner Marx, 1984 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 61)
  - Ivanov, Georgi.Notes of a People's Judge, 1950 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 62)
  - Jacob, Paul.Les lois de l'occupation en France, 1942 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 63)
  - Jenks, C. Wilfred.The Significance for International Law of the Tripartite Character of the International Labor Organization, 1936 May (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 64)
  - Johnson, Alvin S.New World for Old. A Family Migration, 1965 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 65)
  - Kaplan, Morton A.United States Foreign Policy in a Revolutionary Age, 1961 September 15 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 66)
  - Karp, Basil.The Draft Constitution for a European Political Community, 1954 May (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 67)
  - Kellor, Frances and Martin Domke.Arbitration in International Controversy, Undated (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 68)
  - Kelsen, Hans.Aperçu d'une théorie générale de l'État, 1927 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 69)
  - Kelsen, Hans.Beiträge zur Kritik des Rechtsgutachtens über die Frage der österreichischen Staatsbürgerschaft des Fürsten von Thurn und Taxis, 1924 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 70)
  - Kelsen, Hans.La Dictature de parti, 1934 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 71)
  - Kelsen, Hans.Grundriß einer allgemeinen Theorie des Staates, 1926 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 72)
  - Kelsen, Hans.Juristischer Formalismus und Reine Rechtslehre, 1929 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 73)
  - Kelsen, Hans.Der Staat als Übermensch. Eine Erwiderung, 1926 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 74)
  - Kelsen, Hans.Der Wandel des Souveränitätsbegriffes, 1931 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 75)
  - Kelsen, Hans.Was ist Gerechtigkeit?, 1953 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 76)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita S.The Crimes of the Stalin Era. Special Report to the 20th Congress of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union, 1956 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 77)
  - Khrushchev, N.S.Disarmament for Durable Peace and Friendship, 1960 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 78)
  - Kirchheimer, Otto.Gegenwartsprobleme der Asylgewährung, 1959 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 79)
  - Kirchheimer, Otto.Weimar ... und was dann?, 1930 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 80)
  - Kiser, Margaret.Organization of American States. A Handbook for Use in Schools, Colleges and Adult Study Groups, 1955 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 81)
  - Klineberg, Otto.Race and Psychology, 1958 May (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 82)
  - Kommission der europäischen Gemeinschaften.Bericht der Kommission über Die Europäische Union, 1975 June 25 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 83)
  - Kozlov, F.Modificaciones en los Estatutos del partido comunista de la Union Sovietica, 1961 October 28 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 84)
  - Kranzbühler, Otto.Rückblick auf Nürnberg, 1949 September (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 85)
  - Kunz, Josef L.The Mexican Expropriations, 1940 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 86)
  - Kunz, Josef L.Teoria General del Derecho Internacional, 1952 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 87)
  - Laserson, Max M.The Development of Soviet Foreign Policy in Europe, 1917-1942, 1943 January (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 88)
  - Laski, Harold J.On the Study of Politics. An Inaugural Lecture Delivered at the London School of Economics and Political Science on 22 October 1926 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 89)
  - Laski, Harold J.Russia and the West. Policy for Britain, 1947 November (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 90)
  - Lawyers Committee on Blockades.The United Nations and the Egyptian Blockade of The Suez Canal, 1953 June 29 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 91)
  - League of Nations.Members of the League and Composition of the Council, 1937 October 18 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 92)
  - Leibholz, Gerhard.Demokratie und Rechtsstaat, 1957 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 93)
  - Lindenberg, Hermann Meyer.Las Instituciones de Derecho Internacional en las Constituciones de Colombia, 1952 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 94)
  - Lipetsker, Mikhail S.Property Rights of Soviet Citizens, 1946 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 95)
  - Lloyd, William B. Jr.Peace Requires Peacmakers, 1964 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 96)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot Jr.You ... and the United Nations 1956. Henry Cabot Lodge Jr. U.S. Representative to the UN answers your questions (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 97)
  - Luce, Henry R. et al.Dumbarton Oaks and San Francisco, 1945 May (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 98)
  - Lysenko, Trofim.The Science of Biology Today, 1948 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 99)
  - The Manchester Guardian.The Record on Suez. A Chronology of Events. An Economic Reckoning. Leading Articles. Low, 1956 November (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 100)
  - Marshall, Charles Burton.Crisis Over Rhodesia: A Skeptical View, 1967 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 101)
  - Marshall, Charles Burton.Cuba: Thoughts Prompted by the Crisis, 1962 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 102)
  - Matthews, Mary Alice.Neutrality. Select list of references on neutrality and the policy of the United States in the World War and Post War Periods, 1938 September 26 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 103)
  - McMahon, Brien.The Hydrogen Bomb. A Plan for Atomic Peace, 1950 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 104)
  - Mezerik, A.G. (ed.)Colonialism and the United Nations, 1964 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 105)
  - Michael, Donald N.Cybernation: The Silent Conquest, 1962 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 106)
  - Miller, D.F.What Laws Can the Church Change?, 1955 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 107)
  - Miller, Herbert Adolphus.The Bulwark of Freedom, 1918 October 03 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 108)
  - Millis, Walter.A World Without War, 1961 (Box 25 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 109)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J.Conduct of American Foreign Policy, 1949 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 1)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J.The Crisis of Communism, 1965 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 2)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J.The New Atlantic Community, 1961 April (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 3)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J. T he Real Issue between Russia and the United States, 1951 January 18 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 4)
  - Morley, Felix.Humanity Tries Again. An Analysis of the United Nations Charter, 1946 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 5)
  - Moslar, Hermann.Das Völkerrecht in der Praxis der deutschen Gerichte, 1957 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 6)
  - Muir, Ramsey.The Character of the British Empire, 1917 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 7)
  - Murray, John Courtney.Morality and Modern War, 1959 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 8)
  - Murville, Maurice Couve de.Address By His Excellency Maurice Couve de Murville, French Minister of Foreign Affairs Before the Special Session of The United Nations General Assembly On June 22, 1967, Undated (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 9)
  - Murville, Maurice Couve de.Address By His Excellency Maurice Couve de Murville, French Minister of Foreign Affairs On the Middle East Crisis Before the French National Assembly On Wednesday, June 7, 1967, Undated (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 10)
  - Mussolini, Arnaldo.Die Arbeitsverfassung. Einleitung und Betrachtungen, 1933 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 11)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ.The Right to Strike and the General Welfare, 1967 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 12)
  - Nawaz Jung, Nawab Moin.Hyderabad in Fetters, 1952 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 13)
  - Nawaz Jung, Nawab Moin.Hyderabad under Military Occupation, 1951 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 14)
  - Nawiasky, Hans.Die Demokratie in der Schweiz, 1951 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 15)
  - Nawiasky, Hans.Die Zukunft der politischen Parteien, 1924 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 16)
  - Nef, John Ulric.The Universities Look for Unity, 1943 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 17)
  - Nehru, Jawaharlal.Asian-African Conference. April 18-24, 1955. Prime Minister Jawaharlal Nehru's Speeches. The Final Communique, 1955 May (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 18)
  - Neuwirth, Gösta.Franz Schreker, 1959 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 19)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold.The Moral Implications Of Loyalty To The United Nations, 1952 July (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 20)
  - Nixon, Richard M.The Rule of Law. Text of Address of The Vice President of the United States before The Academy of Political Science, 1959 April 13 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 21)
  - Nomad, Max.The Jewish Conspiracy, 1944 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 22)
  - Novick, Paul and J. M. Budish.Jews in the Soviet Union. Citizens and Builders, 1948 May (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 23)
  - O'Donnell, Charles P. and The Post-War World Committee.Transition from War to Peace, 1943 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 25)
  - Oesterreicher, John M.The Brotherhood of Christians and Jews, 1964 April (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 26)
  - Oesterreicher, John M.The Conciliar Statement on the Jews, 1966 February (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 27)
  - Osgood, Robert E.Nuclear Control in NATO, 1962 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 28)
  - Pan American Union.Alliance for Progress. Official Documents Emanating from the Special Meeting of the Inter-American Economic and Social Council at the Ministerial Level. Held in Punta del Este, Uruguay from August 5 to 17, 1961 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 29)
  - Pan American Union.American Treaty on Pacific Settlement. Pact of Bogotá, March 30-May 2, 1948 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 30)
  - Pan American Union.Charter of the Organization of American States. Signed at the Ninth International Conference of American States, Bogotá, March 30-May 2, 1948 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 31)
  - Pan American Union.Eighth International Conference of American States, Lima, Peru, December 9-27, 1938. Report on the Results of the Conference, 1939 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 32)
  - Pan American Union.Final Act of the Ninth International Conference of American States. Bogotá, Colombia, March 30-May 2, 1948 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 33)
  - Pan American Union.Inter-American Conference for the Maintenance of Peace. Buenos Aires, December 1-23, 1936. Report on the Proceedings of the Conference, 1937 February (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 34)
  - Pan American Union.Pan American Postwar Organization. Observations and Suggestions of the Executive Committee on Problems of the Governing Board of the Pan American Union, 1944 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 35)
  - Pan American Union.Report on the Meeting of the Ministers of Foreign Affairs of the American Republics. Panama, September 23-October 3, 1939 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 36)
  - Pan American Union.Report on the Second Meeting of the Ministers of Foreign Affairs of the American Republics. Habana, July 21-30, 1940 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 37)
  - Paresce, Enrico.Giorgio Sorel, 1934 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 38)
  - Peter, F. X.Shall Switzerland Surrender Its German-Owned Property?, 1946 January 10 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 39)
  - Pineau, Christian.The Algerian Problem, 1957 February (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 40)
  - Porter, Paul A.The Gulf of Aqaba: An International Waterway. Its Significance to International Trade, 1957 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 41)
  - The Proportional Representation Society.The Safeguard of Parliamentary Government: Constitutional Reform, 1934 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 42)
  - Rathjens, George W.The Future of the Strategic Arms Race. Options for the 1970s, 1969 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 43)
  - Reiff, Henry.Transition from League of Nations to United Nations, 1946 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 44)
  - Rocca, Helen M.Nominating Methods. With Special Reference to the Direct Primary, 1927 April (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 45)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A.Address of Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller of New York at the 69th Annual Meeting, American Political Science Association, Fairmont-Roosevelt Hotel, New Orleans, Louisiana, Wednesday, September 5, 1973 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 46)
  - Rudd, Herbert F.A Method of Balanced Representation, 1944 August (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 47)
  - Rudzinski, Aleksander.Admission of New Members. The United Nations and the League of Nations, 1952 April (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 48)
  - Salvin, Marina.The North Atlantic Pact, 1949 May (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 49)
  - Scheer, Robert.How the United States Got Involved in Vietnam, 1965 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 50)
  - Schröer, Arnold.Über die Sprache als Kunst und die Weltmacht-Stellung der Engländer, 1922 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 51)
  - Schwiegler, Gebhard.German Foreign Policy, 1975 February (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 52)
  - Seydoux, Roger.Statement on the United Nations Peace-Keeping Operations, 1965 May 17 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 53)
  - Silveira, Alipio.Professor Clovis Bevilaqua's Political And Juristic Thought, 1945 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 54)
  - Sinclair, Keith.Imperial Federation. A Study of New Zealand Policy and Opinion 1880-1914, 1955 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 55)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Arms Limitation and Disarmament. Seventeenth Strategy for Peace Conference Report. October 7-10 1976 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 56)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Coordination of the Economic and Social Activities of the United Nations. Tenth Conference on the United Nations of the Next Decade, Baden bei Wien, Austria, June 22-29, 1975 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 57)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Decision-Making Processes of the United Nations. Ninth Conference on the United Nations of the Next Decade. Vail, Colorado, June 9-16, 1974 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 58)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Managing Interdependence. Eleventh Conference on the United Nations of the Next Decade, Charlottesville, Virginia, U.S.A., June 27-July 3, 1976 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 59)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Multilateral Disarmament and the Special Session. Twelfth Conference on the United Nations of the Next Decade, 1977 June (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 60)
  - The Stanley Foundation.New Aspects of the International Protection of Human Rights. Twenty-fifth Report of the Commission to Study the Organization of Peace, 1977 June (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 61)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Peace and Security: New Opportunities. Eighth Conference On the United Nations of the Next Decade, Amalfi, Italy, June 24-30, 1973 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 62)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Report of the Fourth Annual Conference on United Nations Procedures. New Paltz, New York, May 4-7, 1973 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 63)
  - The Stanley Foundation.Strategy for Peace 1985. Report of the Twenty-Sixth Annual Strategy for Peace US Foreign Policy Conference October 24-26, 1985 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 64)
  - The Stanley Foundation.The United States and the Future of the Nonproliferation Regime. Report of a Vantage Conference, Cooperstown, New York, May 13-16, 1984, 1984 May (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 65)
  - Stourzh, Gerald.The Case of the Toppling Idol, 1958 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 66)
  - Strisower, Leo.Die Gestaltung der völkerrechtlichen Verhältnisse in Vorderasien im letzten Menschenalter vor dem Kriege, 1916 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 67)
  - Subcommittee on the United Nations Charter.Staff Study No. 1: The Problem of the Veto in the United Nations Security Council, 1954 February 19 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 68)
  - Subcommittee on the United Nations Charter.Staff Study No. 2: How the United Nations Charter Has Developed, 1954 May 18 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 69)
  - Subcommittee on the United Nations Charter.Staff Study No. 3: The Problem of Membership in the United Nations, 1954 May 21 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 70)
  - Subcommittee on the United Nations Charter.Staff Study No. 5: Pacific Settlement of Disputes in the United Nations, 1954 October 17 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 71)
  - Subcommittee on the United Nations Charter.Staff Study No. 6: Budgetary and Financial Problems of the United Nations, 1954 December (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 72)
  - Subcommittee on the United Nations Charter.Final Report: Review of the United Nations Charter, 1956 April 23 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 73)
  - Sulkowski, Joseph.Dumbarton Oaks. An Alliance of Great Powers or An International Organization Based on Law, 1945 January (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 74)
  - Sumberg, Theodore A.Freedom in the Third World, 1975 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 75)
  - Supreme Court of the United States.Brief of American Jewish Committee and Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith as Amici Curiae, 1962 October (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 76)
  - Supreme Court of the United States.Brief of Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, American Civil Liberties Union and American Jewish Committee as Amici Curiae, 1968 October (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 77)
  - Supreme Court of the United States.Motion for Leave to File Brief and Brief for the American Association for the United Nations as Amicus Curiae, 1947 October (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 78)
  - Taylor, Edmund.The Real Case Against Nasser, ca. 1957 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 79)
  - Thompson, Kenneth W.Higher Education for National Development: One Model for Technical Assistance, 1972 November (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 80)
  - Tsunts, M., I. Furman, S. Yezerskaya.Personal Property in the Soviet Union, 1960 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 81)
  - Tucker, Robert W.Just War and Vatican Council II: A Critique, 1966 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 82)
  - United Nations.Administrative Tribunal. Statute and Rules, 1950 July (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 83)
  - United Nations.Agreement Between the United Nations and the International Labour Organization, 1947 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 84)
  - United Nations, Office of Public Information.Apartheid in Practice, 1971 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 85)
  - United Nations, Office of Public Information.Declaration on the Strengthening of International Security, 1971 March (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 86)
  - United Nations.Draft. International Covenants on Human Rights, 1954 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 87)
  - United Nations.The Economic and Social Council, 1949 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 88)
  - United Nations.The Indispensable Role of the United Nations. A Difficult Year in Review, 1957 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 89)
  - United Nations, Office of Public Information.Infringements of Trade Union Rights in Southern Africa, 1970 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 90)
  - United Nations.The International Court of Justice, 1957 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 91)
  - United Nations.New Challenge for the United Nations, 1971 February (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 92)
  - United Nations.Our Rights as Human Beings. Teaching about the United Nations and the Specialized Agencies. A Discussion Guide, 1955 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 93)
  - United Nations, Department of Public Information.The Price of Peace. A Symposium, 1951 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 94)
  - United Nations, Department of Public Information.The Problem of Hungary. A Summary of the Report of the General Assembly's Special Committee, 1957 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 95)
  - United Nations, Information Office.Punishment for War Crimes, 1942 July (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 96)
  - United Nations.Report of the Sub-Committee on the Situation in Angola, 1962 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 97)
  - United Nations, Department of Public Information.Scientific and Technical Aspects of the Control of Atomic Energy, 1946 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 98)
  - United Nations, General Assembly. International Law Commission. Survey of International Law in Relation to the Work of Codification of the International Law Commission, 1949 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 99)
  - United Nations, Office of Public Information.Treaty on the Prohibition of the Emplacement of Nuclear Weapons and Other Weapons of Mass Destruction on the Sea-Bed and the Ocean Floor and in the Subsoil Thereof, 1971 March (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 100)
  - United Nations.United Nations Conference on Freedom of Information Held at Geneva, Switzerland, from 23 March to 21 April, 1948. Final Act (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 101)